Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts, 1924-1957 RL.11870
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Radio Contracts, 1927-1948; undated; 4
  - Standard Brands, 1930-1948; 173
    - Miscellaneous folios, 1947 (Film-reel 443)
    - Muriel Kirkland, 1943-1944 (Film-reel 408)
    - One Man's Family and cut-ins, 1948 (Film-reel 443)
    - Orson Welles, 1945 Dec. 2-16 (Film-reel 408)
    - Paul Whiteman, 1943 (Film-reel 409)
    - Pied Pipers, 1943 (Film-reel 409)
    - Ray Noble, 1941-1947 (Film-reel 409)
    - Ray Perkins--Option for Fleischmann's Yeast, 1930 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 254)
    - Robert Shaw Chorale, 1948 (Film-reel 443)
    - Royal Baking Powder in Africa, 1948 (Film-reel 443)
    - Shirley Booth, 1945 (Film-reel 408)
    - Soldiers with Coupons folios, 1945 May-July (Film-reel 403)
    - Soldiers with Coupons folios, 1945 May-July (Film-reel 404)
    - Spike Jones and the City Slickers, 1945 (Film-reel 409)
    - The Man Called X--Consent, 1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Tommy Dorsey, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Tony Romano, 1945 (Film-reel 409)
  - Standard Brands--Bakers of America, 1943-1944; 174
    - Bill Goodwin, 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Bing Crosby, 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Bob Burns, 1943 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - Bob Hope, 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Burns and Allen, 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Don Ameche, 1943 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - Dorothy Lamour, 1943 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - Dudley Chambers, 1943 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1943 Dec. 21; 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Fred Allen, 1943 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - Gracie Fields, 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Hollywood Restaurant--Consent, 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1943 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - Judy Garland, 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Ray Noble, 1943 Dec. 21; 1944 June 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Spike Jones, 1943 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 403)
  - Standard Brands--Chase & Sanborn, 1937-1942; 175
    - Albert E. Wiggam, 1941 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 254)
    - All Quiet on the Western Front--Consent, 1937 Oct. 12 (Film-reel 254)
    - Edgar Bergen, 1941 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 254)
    - John Carradine, 1942 May 30 (Film-reel 254)
    - Laird Cregar, 1942 May 19 (Film-reel 254)
    - Mr. and Mrs. J.E. Jordan, 1941 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 254)
  - Standard Brands--Chase & Sanborn--Alec Templeton Program, 1946; 176
    - Clark Dennis, 1946 June 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Eugenie Baird, 1946 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 404)
    - Evelyn Knight, 1946 July 7 (Film-reel 404)
    - Jean Tighe, 1946 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 404)
    - Jo Stafford, 1946 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 404)
    - Kay Armen, 1946 June 16 (Film-reel 404)
    - Kay Lorraine, 1946 June 9 (Film-reel 404)
    - Margaret Whiting, 1946 June 30 (Film-reel 404)
    - Martha Tilton, 1946 Aug. 25 (Film-reel 404)
    - Milena Miller, 1946 July 14 (Film-reel 404)
    - Patti Clayton, 1946 June 2 (Film-reel 404)
    - Pearl Bailey, 1946 July 21 (Film-reel 404)
    - Peggy Lee, 1946 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 404)
    - Vera Holly, 1946 July 28 (Film-reel 404)
  - Standard Brands--Chase & Sanborn--Edgar Bergen Program, 1941-1944; 177
    - Alan Reed (Falstaff), 1944 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 404)
    - Anita Ellis, 1944 Jan. 23-Feb. 20 (Film-reel 404)
    - Ann Sothern, 1942 Feb. 4; 12 (Film-reel 254)
    - Anne Baxter, 1944 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 404)
    - As a Draft Board Might Be But Isn't--Consent, 1943 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 254)
    - Barbara Stanwyck, 1943 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 254)
    - Basil Rathbone, 1944 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 404)
    - Bert Lahr, 1942-1943 (Film-reel 254)
    - Betty Grable, 1941 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 254)
    - Bill Thompson, 1943 Feb. 3-May 13 (Film-reel 254)
    - Bob Burns, 1944 June 11 (Film-reel 404)
    - Carmen Miranda, 1942 May 15; 1943 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 254)
    - Carmen Miranda, 1944 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 404)
    - Cecil B. DeMille, 1942 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 254)
    - Cecil B. DeMille, 1944 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 404)
    - Charles Boyer, 1943 May 13 (Film-reel 254)
    - Charles Laughton, 1944 Dec. 24 (Film-reel 404)
    - Charles Ruggles, 1942 Aug. 24; 1943 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 254)
    - Charles Ruggles, 1944 Jan. 2; Mar. 12 (Film-reel 404)
    - Chester Morris, 1942 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 254)
    - Claudette Colbert, 1943 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 254)
    - Clyde Beatty, 1944 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1943 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 254)
    - Don Ameche, 1942 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 254)
    - Don Ameche, 1944 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 404)
    - Donald Crisp, 1942 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 254)
    - Dorothy Lamour, 1944 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 404)
    - Ed Gardner, 1944 May 7-Sept. 10 (Film-reel 404)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1944 July 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Edgar M. Wooley (Monty), 1942 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 254)
    - Edward Arnold, 1942 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 254)
    - Edward Everett Horton, 1942 Apr. 23; Nov. 25 (Film-reel 254)
    - Edward Everett Horton, 1944 Feb. 13; Aug. 27 (Film-reel 404)
    - Elsa Maxwell, 1944 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 404)
    - Eve Arden, 1944 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 404)
    - Fats Waller, 1943 Nov. 22 (Film-reel 254)
    - Folios, 1942-1943 (Film-reel 254)
    - Folios, 1944 July-Dec. (Film-reel 404)
    - Frank Fay, 1944 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 404)
    - Gary Cooper, 1942 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 254)
    - Gene Krupa, 1942 Dec. 18; 31 (Film-reel 254)
    - Gene Lockhart, 1944 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 404)
    - George Raft, 1942 Jan. 11 (Film-reel 254)
    - Gertrude Niesen, 1944 Oct. 15 (Film-reel 404)
    - Ginny Simms, 1942 May 20; 1943 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 254)
    - Greer Garson, 1943 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 254)
    - Greer Garson, 1944 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 404)
    - Hal Peary (Gildersleeve), 1942 Sept. 11 (Film-reel 254)
    - Hal Peary (Gildersleeve), 1944 July 2 (Film-reel 404)
    - Hedy Lamarr, 1942 Jan. 26; Sept. 15 (Film-reel 254)
    - Ida Lupino, 1942-1943 (Film-reel 254)
    - Irene Dunne, 1943 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 254)
    - Irwin Corey, 1944 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 404)
    - Jack Carson, 1944 July 9 (Film-reel 404)
    - James Melton, 1944 May 21 (Film-reel 404)
    - James Newell, 1942 June 9 (Film-reel 254)
    - Jane Powell, 1944 Mar. 5; Apr. 16 (Film-reel 404)
    - Jane Withers, 1942 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 254)
    - Jeanette MacDonald, 1942 Mar. 13; 1943 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 254)
    - Jim Ameche, 1944 Oct. 15-Nov. 26 (Film-reel 404)
    - Jim Ameche, Billie Burke, 1944 Oct. 22 (Film-reel 404)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1944 July 30 (Film-reel 404)
    - Joan Blondell, 1942 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 254)
    - John Robert Powers, 1944 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 404)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1943 Jan. 11 (Film-reel 254)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1944 Oct. 8 (Film-reel 404)
    - Judy Garland, 1942 June 3 (Film-reel 254)
    - Judy Garland, 1944 June 23; Sept. 3 (Film-reel 404)
    - June Powell, 1944 Jan. 2; 9 (Film-reel 404)
    - Ken Murray, 1942 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 254)
    - Lauritz Melchior, 1944 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 404)
    - Lena Horne, 1943 Dec. 1; 13 (Film-reel 254)
    - Leo Carrillo, 1944 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 404)
    - Louella Parsons, 1942 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 254)
    - Lucille Ball, 1942 Apr. 19 (Film-reel 254)
    - Lucille Ball, 1944 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 404)
    - Lupe Velez, 1943 Mar. 13; Dec. 6 (Film-reel 254)
    - Marjorie Main, 1942 Nov. 14; 25 (Film-reel 254)
    - Marlin Hart, 1944 Aug. 6 (Film-reel 404)
    - Martha Raye, 1943 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 254)
    - Mary Boland, 1943 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 254)
    - Mike Romanoff, 1944 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 404)
    - Nelson Eddy, 1942 (Film-reel 254)
    - Olivia de Havilland, 1944 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 404)
    - Orson Welles, 1944 Apr. 2-Nov. 5 (Film-reel 404)
    - Paulette Goddard, 1943 Jan. 6; Dec. 3 (Film-reel 254)
    - Paulette Goddard, 1944 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 404)
    - Pick-Up--Consent, 1943 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 254)
    - Rags Ragland, 1943 May 8 (Film-reel 254)
    - Rita Hayworth, 1942 June 12; Sept. 4 (Film-reel 254)
    - Ronald Colman, 1943 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 254)
    - Roy Rogers, 1943 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 254)
    - Roy Rogers, 1944 Aug. 6 (Film-reel 404)
    - Rudy Vallee, 1944 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 404)
    - Ruth Hussey, 1944 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 404)
    - Sidney Greenstreet, 1943 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 254)
    - Signe Hasso, 1944 May 14; Dec. 10 (Film-reel 404)
    - Sir Cedric Hardwicke, 1942 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 254)
    - Susan Burce (later known as Jane Powell), 1943 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 254)
    - Susan Hayward, 1944 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 404)
    - Teresa Wright, 1943 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 254)
    - The King Sisters, 1944 May 7-Sept. 3 (Film-reel 404)
    - Veronica Lake, 1943 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 254)
    - W.C. Fields, 1942 Nov. 1 (Film-reel 254)
    - W.C. Fields, 1944 Feb. 20; Mar. 26 (Film-reel 404)
    - Walter Brennan, 1942 June 19 (Film-reel 254)
    - Walter Pidgeon, 1943 May 22 (Film-reel 254)
    - William Bendix, 1944 July 16 (Film-reel 404)
    - Yvette, 1944 Apr. 23; 30 (Film-reel 404)
    - Zeppo Marx--Ray Milland, 1944 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 404)
  - Standard Brands--Chase & Sanborn--Paul Whiteman Program, 1942-1943; 178
    - Al Rinker, 1943 July 2 (Film-reel 254)
    - Bert Lahr, 1943 July 7 (Film-reel 254)
    - Bob Burns, 1943 June 25 (Film-reel 254)
    - Ed Gardner, 1943 July 8 (Film-reel 254)
    - Eddie Cantor, 1943 May 19 (Film-reel 254)
    - Folios, 1942 June 6 (Film-reel 254)
    - George Burns, Gracie Allen, 1943 May 19; July 7 (Film-reel 254)
    - Jimmy Dorsey, 1943 Aug. 22 (Film-reel 254)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1943 July 1 (Film-reel 254)
    - Lou Holtz, 1943 June 25 (Film-reel 254)
    - Mrs. Edna Skelton (Red Skelton also, but he did not sign), 1943 May 20; June 2 (Film-reel 254)
    - Ole Olsen, Chic Johnson, 1943 July 7 (Film-reel 254)
    - Roy Bargy, 1943 Aug. 2 (Film-reel 254)
    - The Modernaires, 1943 July 23 (Film-reel 254)
  - Standard Brands--Edgar Bergen License Agreements, 1937-1938; 179
    - Cohn and Rosenberger (Jewelry), 1937 Aug. 2 (Film-reel 409)
    - Collegeville Flag and Mfg. (Flags, costumes), 1937 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 409)
    - Eberhard Faber Pencil, 1937 (Film-reel 409)
    - Fleischaker and Baum (Dolls), 1937 June 1 (Film-reel 409)
    - Herz and Kory (Leather goods), 1938 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 409)
    - John C. Wolwood (Textiles), 1937 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 409)
    - Kerk Guild (Soap figurines), 1937 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 409)
    - Libbey-Owens Glass, 1938 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 409)
    - McLoughlin Manufacturing, 1938 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 409)
    - Western Tablet and Stationery, 1937 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 409)
    - White and Wyckoff (Paper products), 1938 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 409)
    - Whitman Publishing, 1938 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 409)
  - Standard Brands--Mary Marlin, 1943-1945; 180
    - Folios, 1943 Sept. 29-1944 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 409)
    - OK'd estimates, 1945 Jan.-July (Film-reel 409)
    - Stella Radio Enterprises, 1943-1945 (Film-reel 409)
    - Writers contracts, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 409)
  - Swift & Co., 1941-1944; 181
    - Allsweet spots folios, 1942 June-July (Film-reel 254)
    - Breakfast Club folios, 1941 Apr. 4-May 3 (Film-reel 254)
    - Chicago Office memo on estimates, 1944 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 254)
    - Revised estimate for Jewel Shortening, 1943 Dec. 21-1944 June 16 (Film-reel 254)
    - Yours Truly folios, 1941 Apr. 4; 14 (Film-reel 254)
  - Textron, 1945-1946; 182
    - Clare Booth Luce, 1945 (Film-reel 409)
    - Frank Gallup, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Helen Hayes, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Louis Calhoun, 1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - The Two Mrs. Carrolls--Rights, 1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - What Every Woman Knows--Rights, 1945 (Film-reel 409)
    - Wladimir Sclinsky, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 409)
  - Textron--Textron Theatre, 1945-1946; 183
    - A Child Is Born--Rights, 1945 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 409)
    - A Doll's House--Rights, 1946 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 409)
    - Alfred Drake, 1945 Nov. 10; Dec. 29 (Film-reel 409)
    - Angel Street--Rights, 1945 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 409)
    - Ann Rutledge--Rights, 1946 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 409)
    - Arrowsmith--Rights, 1945 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 409)
    - Blithe Spirit--Rights, 1945 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 409)
    - Boris Karloff, 1945 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 409)
    - Brian Aherne, 1945 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 409)
    - Burgess Meredith, 1945 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 409)
    - Chopsticks--Rights, 1945 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 409)
    - Dean Jagger, 1945 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 409)
    - Family Portrait--Rights, 1946 Jan. 17 (Film-reel 409)
    - Folios, 1945 Sept. 8-1946 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 409)
    - Happy Journey to Trenton and Camden--Rights, 1945 Dec. 1 (Film-reel 409)
    - Intermezzo--Rights, 1945 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 409)
    - Jane Eyre--Rights, 1946 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 409)
    - Jose Ferrer, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Karl Swenson, 1945 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 409)
    - Kind Lady--Rights, 1946 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 409)
    - Let the Hurricane Roar--Rights, 1945 Sept. 22; 1946 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 409)
    - Madame Curie--Rights, 1945 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 409)
    - Martin Gabel, 1945 Nov. 24; 1946 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 409)
    - Maurice Evans, 1945 Nov. 17; 1946 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 409)
    - Michael O'Shea, 1945 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 409)
    - Miss Rudebaker Takes Off--Rights, 1945 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 409)
    - My Little Boy--Rights, 1946 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 409)
    - Of Men and Minerva--Rights, 1946 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 409)
    - Otto Kruger, 1946 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 409)
    - Ralph Bellamy, 1945 Sept. 22 (Film-reel 409)
    - Reconversion of Susan--Rights, 1946 Jan. 5 (Film-reel 409)
    - Shadow Play--Rights, 1945 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 409)
    - Sir Cedric Hardwicke, 1945 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 409)
    - Sobbin' Women--Rights, 1946 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 409)
    - The Ghost and Mrs. Muir--Rights, 1945 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 409)
    - The Heart Ungiven--Rights, 1945 Nov. 15 (Film-reel 409)
    - The Late Christopher Bean--Rights, 1945 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 409)
    - To the Ladies--Rights, 1945 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 409)
    - Tom Helmore, 1946 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 409)
    - Tonio Selwart, 1945 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 409)
    - Victoria Regina--Rights, 1945 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 409)
    - Walter Huston, 1945 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 409)
    - Wendell Corey, 1946 Jan. 26 (Film-reel 409)
    - Wuthering Heights--Rights, 1945 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 409)
  - Textron--This Is Helen Hayes, 1945; 184
    - Audition folios, 1945 Aug. 31-Sept. 4 (Film-reel 409)
    - Folios, 1945 (Film-reel 409)
    - Loretta Young, 1945 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 409)
    - Shock Nurse--Rights, 1945 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 409)
    - Solace at Iwo--Rights, 1945 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 409)
  - U.S. Brewing Industry Foundation, 1942-1943; 185
    - Joe Marsh folios, 1942 Aug. 14; Nov. 12 (Film-reel 254)
    - Parker Fennelly folios, 1943 Mar. 29; June 16 (Film-reel 254)
  - U.S. Government, 1944; 186
    - Office of War Information--Permission from Lever Brothers to translate some Lux Radio Theatre scripts into French for broadcasting, 1944 Aug. 24 (Film-reel 409)
    - Recordings folio, 1944 July 7-Aug. 4 (Film-reel 409)
  - U.S. Playing Cards, 1941; 187
    - Folios, 1941 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 254)
  - United Hospital Fund of New York, 1944; 188
    - Show folios, 1944 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 409)
  - Universal Pictures, 1941; 1944; 189
    - Folios, 1944 June 22 (Film-reel 409)
    - Helzapoppin folios, 1941 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 254)
  - W.K. Kellogg Co., 1942-1943; 190
    - Cancellation memo, 1943 Oct. 4 (Film-reel 252)
    - Folios, 1942 May 11 (Film-reel 252)
  - Ward Baking, 1943-1947; 191
    - Bruce Eliot, 1943 (Film-reel 410)
    - Dinner at Hotel Commodore folio, 1944 Sept. 11 (Film-reel 410)
    - Don McLaughlin, 1946-1947 (Film-reel 409)
    - Elton Britt, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Folios, 1945 Aug. 24-Nov. 30 (Film-reel 409)
    - Howard Carraway, 1945 (Film-reel 409)
    - Judy and Jane folios, 1943 (Film-reel 410)
    - Layman Cameron, 1945-1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Miscellaneous, 1943 June 21-1944 May 31 (Film-reel 410)
    - Sheldon Stark, 1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Tennessee Jed facilities, 1946 (Film-reel 409)
    - Tennessee Jed folios, 1945 Dec. 3-1946 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 410)
    - Terry and the Pirates folios, 1943 (Film-reel 410)
    - Tip Top Quiz folio, 1944 (Film-reel 410)
  - Warner Bros. Pictures, 1927; 1941; 192
    - Folios, 1941 May 20-July 14 (Film-reel 254)
    - Letter regarding W. and R. Mauch, 1927 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 254)
  - Washington State Apples, 1940-1941; 193
    - Folios, 1940 Dec.-1941 Feb. 17 (Film-reel 254)
  - Weco Products, 1944; 194
    - Hair Nets fashion show folios, 1944 May 2 (Film-reel 409)
  - William Wrigley Jr. Co., 1939; 1943; 195
    - Folios, 1943 Jan. 3-Aug. 1 (Film-reel 254)
    - Gene Autry, 1939 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 254)
  - Wine Institute, 1943; 196
    - Folios, 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 254)